

About Me

I approach every project, striving to understand how to create solutions that don't just look good but truly connect with people.

I thrive in collaborative environments where different perspectives come together to build something greater, and I am always excited to take on projects that challenge me to grow.

Contact

+45 31 36 73 07

kiameggele@gmail.com <u>Portfolio</u>

Experience with

- Web Design
- Frontend Development
- UX Research
- UX/UI Design
- Marketing
- Concept Development

Language

- English
- Danish

Kia Meggele

Digital Concept Development Student

Education

Copenhagen School of Design and Technology

PBA in Digital Concept
 Development

AP Graduate in Multimedia 2022 - 2024

KVUC, HF

Design

• Upper Secondary Education 2020 - 2022

Matas

Materalist Education
2016 - 2018

Experience

Tutor at KEA

• Multimediadesign tutor 2024 - Now

Wonderworks

• Creative Lead 2024 - Now

Matas

• Part Time Sales Assistent 2020 - 2023

• Full Time Sales Assistant 2018 - 2020